yout.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy policy | Yout

Your privacy is very important to us at Yout. This Privacy Policy document outlines what data Yout receives and how we store, manage, and protect it.

This policy is subject to change at any time, for any reason. This policy was last updated on January, 9th 2016.

### Logs

Yout uses log files, which are files that record information including requested webpage resources, IP addresses, browser types, and timestamps. This information is used by Yout for troubleshooting, service analysis, and site maintenance. This information cannot be directly linked to personally identifiable information.

Log files, and any data therein, are not shared with any third party.

### Collected Information

Yout receives and stores information that you enter on the website. This includes requested resources, search queries, and DVR settings. This information is stored to monitor and analyse service activity. This information cannot be linked to personally identifiable information.

All information you enter is voluntary. None of this information is shared with any third party.

### Cookies

Yout stores your preferences in cookies. While these cookies improve your experience by remembering your settings, they're completely optional. All of Yout's features and services work without cookies.

Cookies may be stored by third parties via third party content embedded in Yout, like multimedia players, analytics, and advertisements. Yout has no control over the cookies stored by third parties.

### Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us.
